# IMAM SULTHONI

#### Frontend Developer

imamsulthoni.amd@gmail.com | +6287727197023 Indramayu, West Java

https://linkedin.com/in/imam-sulthoni https://imam-sulthoni.vercel.app

# Summary

I am used to implementing figma's interface design, responsive, applying semantic HTML, compatible across platforms, and always open to input or feedback from users. In the past two years as a frontend developer, I have used several popular frameworks such as ReactJS, NextJS, VueJS, and NuxtJS but currently focusing on ReactJS and NextJS, and also learning React Native. I have implemented reusable components, state management using Redux, Vuex, and Zustand. In the development process, I am used to the agile method where my team and I work together in each sprint to complete the task. However, continuous learning and exploration is the fuel for continues skill improvement.

## Skills

- HTML CSS
- SCSS
- React.js
- Javascript Typescript
- Next.js
- Vue.js
- Nuxt.js
- Shadcn UI Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- Vuex
  - · Agile/Scrum

Zustand

Redux Toolkit

# **Work Experiences**

#### Frontend Developer (Part time) | Agtran Sdn. Bhd. - Malaysia

September 2023 - November 2023

- Collaboration within the team to streamline project delivery.
- Orchestrated data integration using GraphQI to enhance system efficiency.
- · Utilized a tech stack comprising Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Shadon UI, Zustand, and Typescript to drive robust development and user-centric solutions.

#### Frontend Developer (Full time) | Fishlog - Bogor, Indonesia

December 2022 - November 2023

- · Developed a web application using React.js, React Bootstrap, SCSS, and implemented Redux Saga for efficient state management.
- Integrated diverse data sets through Rest API to optimize system functionality.
- · Collaborated within a team using agile methodology to ensure synchronized efforts and iterative development.

#### Frontend Developer (Full time) | Agtran Sdn. Bhd. - Malaysia

November 2021 - December 2022

- · Developed responsive web-based and mobile applications using some tech stack such as Vue.js, Nuxt.js, and Flutter
- Implemented UI designs from Figma that already created by UI/UX team.
- Ensuring seamless integration of APIs and GraphQl for enhanced functionality and user experience.

#### Programmer (Internship) | PT. Bejana Investidata Globalindo - Bandung, Indonesia

November 2020 - March 2021

- Contributed to the creation of various client applications by addressing bugs and implementing new features.
- Collaborated within an agile team framework and executed UI/UX designs.
- Utilized technology stacks including October CMS, React.js, Codelgniter, and Flutter.

#### **Education**

#### Politeknik Negeri Indramayu | Indramayu, West Java

2018 - 2021

Diploma III Informatics Engineering

Final Project: Implementation of Microservice Architecture in the student tuition payment application at Dar Alguran Arjawinangun Islamic Boarding School.

### Certification

Basic Application Programmer | BNSP - LSP Politeknik Negeri Indramayu

#### Language

Indonesia - Native Language

English - Intermediate

#### **Portfolio**

# **Company Project**

#### Fishlog WMS Web

- · Web application for Fishlog warehouse Management System.
- Built using React.js, and Bootstrap as the UI library, coupled with SCSS.
- Collaborated with PM, QA, and Backend Dev in building this project.
- · Data integration with Rest API.

#### **Agtran Fleetsync Admin**

- · Web application for agtran admin in managing incoming reservations or making revisions, scheduling, master data, etc.
- This web application was created using the Next.js framework (typescript), then the UI framework uses Shadon ui based on Tailwind CSS.
- · Collaborate with Backend Developer in doing data integration.
- · Data integration with GraphQI.

#### Agtran Web | www.agtran.com

- · A website of Agtran Sdn. Bhd. for car rental services, where users can make reservations for the car they want to rent.
- · Created using Nuxt.js framework, and Tailwind CSS for the UI library.

#### **XCESS Mobile App**

- · Mobile application of Agtran Sdn. Bhd. which is used for staff or admin in managing car reservations by users.
- · This application was created using Flutter, and GetX for state management.

# **Personal Project & Playground**

## Personal Website <a href="https://imam-sulthoni.vercel.app/">https://imam-sulthoni.vercel.app/</a>

- Personal website for personal branding, containing information about myself, work experience, and direct contact to my email.
- Created using NextJS (Typescript), with Tailwind CSS ui library, also Framer Motion to add animation to the display component.
- Deployed on Vercel.

#### Weather Info Web <a href="https://react-weather-info.vercel.app/">https://react-weather-info.vercel.app/</a>

- · Website to show information of today weather, and forecast.
- Created using Vite + ReactJS (typescript), with Tailwind CSS ui library.
- API Integration using openwathermap to get today weather and forecast, and for the city location search using geoDB cities from rapidapi.com.
- · Deployed on Vercel.

# ReactJS Dashboard Starter <a href="https://react-tailwind-dashboard-starter.vercel.app/">https://react-tailwind-dashboard-starter.vercel.app/</a>

- A web starter dashboard that can be used if there is work that requires a dashboard view, then this can be used to speed up the layout process, and also menu routing.
- · Created using ReactJS CRA, with Tailwind CSS ui library.
- · Deployed on Vercel.

## Other project & playground on my github

https://github.com/mamsul